Aight so check this out.
We got this whole crew down in the
Ville, right?
There's this one shawty, I'm-a call her Lexi.
was low-key crazy, you feel me?
She went to this high school over in
the Heights.
was like the smart one, always gettin' straight
A's, on god.
but at the same time, fam, she was
all about the drama.
Always stirrin' up somethin', know what I'm sayin'?
This one time, I'm chillin' at my block,
sippin' on a bottle of Purple Drank.
when outta nowhere, I see Lexi poppin' up.
She's all hyped up, talkin' 'bout this secret
she found out.
deadass.
She told me they was gonna bust this
one kid.
name of Rico, think he was an opps.
or somethin', I ain't quite sure.
But what Lexi said next, that's when it
got real intense.
she said this whole crew from the Heights.
was set up, like they was workin' together.
You feel me?
Lexi was like, "We need to do somethin'
about it, homie.".
and I'm just sittin' here thinkin', you know,
"Nah, maybe you should just chill." Next thing
I know.
Lexi and this whole crew from the Ville,
they jump outta nothin', pop up at the
Heights.
where Rico and this other kid, they was
just sittin' there, minding they biz.
And next.
all hell breaks loose, bro.
Bottles flyin', shots get fired.
and then.
Lexi she just up and vanishes.
After that.
shawty's been ghost, man.
and I'm thinkin', I don't know what happened
to her, did she even survive?
Nah, but check this out.
I heard she turned state's evidence.
that's when the DA caught up to her.
You feel me?.
I ain't here to judge, homie, that's what
them streets do.